<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Experiment Game</string>
    <string name="title_activity_question">QuestionActivity</string>

    <string name="intro">You will see a screen with options as shown above.
        Each rectangle corresponds to one choice you can make. To learn more about the options,
        tap on the $ sign for the virtual money you may win (green) or lose (red).
        Tap on the dice for the probability of winning (green) or losing (red) this virtual money.
        You can tap on the symbols as much as you want. When you have decided, tap on the select button.</string>

    <string name="play_game">Play Game</string>
    <string name="quit">Quit</string>
    <string name="sign_in">Sign In</string>
    <string name="sign_out">Sign Out</string>
    <string name="password">neurons</string>
    <string name="BTonOff">Bluetooth</string>

    <string name="demo">TRAINING</string>
    <string name="end_demo">END TRAINING</string>
    <string name="finish_demo">You\'ve finished the training! \n\nGood luck playing!</string>

    <string name="select">Select</string>
    <string name="next_trial">Next</string>
    <string name="stay_longer">Check the attributes carefully!</string>
    <string name="database_error">Something is wrong with storing your result, please try to exit the
        app by licking the square on the bottom and clear the app by swiping it to the left.
        If reopening the app does not solve the problem, please contact the technician. </string>

    <string name="handshake_error">The handshake message does not match!</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_error">The bluetooth is not responsive for over 500 milliseconds!</string>
    <string name="thread_error">The thread is interrupted</string>


    <string name="pop_up_bt">Bluetooth is not connected correctly, try again</string>

    <string name="survey_date">Date: </string>
    <string name="survey_age">Age: </string>
    <string name="survey_language">Are you a native English speaker?</string>
    <string name="survey_hand">Handedness?</string>
    <string name="survey_color">Do you have any form of color blindness?</string>
    <string name="survey_vision">Vision?</string>
    <string name="survey_disease">Do you currently have a diagnosed,
        major neurological or other health condition that affects your
        memory or attention? (other than ADHD, Depression,
        or Autism spectrum disorders) Such as traumatic brain injury,
        multiple sclerosis, chronic fatigue syndrome, Alzheimer’s, Parkinson’s, etc.
        Do not enter epilepsy</string>

    <string name="survey_claim">The National Institutes of Health (NIH),
        the Federal agency that is supporting this research,
        requests information on the gender, racial, and ethnic composition
        of the participants of studies it sponsors. This information is
        collected to ensure that the results of this study can be generalized
        to the population as a whole and do not exclude any ethnic or gender groups.
        You do not have to respond to these questions to participate in experiments
        in the lab. If you choose to respond, please select the relevant
        categories below.</string>
    <string name="survey_personal_info_sex">Sex: </string>
    <string name="survey_personal_info_ethnic">Ethnic Category: </string>
    <string name="survey_personal_info_racial">Racial Category: </string>


</resources>
